<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Duah Philip</title>
    <link>https://Duah-Philip.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://Duah-Philip.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://Duah-Philip.github.io/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://Duah-Philip.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with TU Bergakademie Freiberg</title>
      <link>https://Duah-Philip.github.io/post/interview-daad-preis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Duah-Philip.github.io/post/interview-daad-preis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Q&amp;amp;A with…
&amp;hellip;Philip Duah, Master student (Sustainable Mining and Remediation Management) from Ghana and DAAD award winner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Why did you decide to study at TUBAF?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;My goal was to attend a top mining university that places great emphasis on internationalization, is known for mining research and innovation, and where I can study and conduct research at the intersection of mining, technology, and sustainability. I found out about TUBAF during my search and was immediately convinced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;You won the DAAD award. How are you involved with international students?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;I have been part of the buddy program for new international students since my 2nd semester. I co-founded the Amnesty International university group and was its spokesperson. I also served on a committee of the Student Council (StuRa) and I helped organize the Festival of Cultures. Currently, I offer online consultations for students in my degree program as a tutor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;What opportunities are there to get involved at the university?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;Within the university, we are always looking for committed students to support the committee work in the StuRa and the FSRs. It is also possible to participate in the buddy program to support new international students. Additionally, there are working groups, clubs and initiatives within the university that are always looking for new members. Getting involved in these areas is a form of personal development and is very rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;What tip do you have for international students?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to ask questions. There is a lot of support here. You can always contact the International University Center. Without its support, for example, I would not have been able to complete my second internship. The Career Center also supports international students and already invited us to a meeting to better understand our career needs and to work out new strategies.
For me, TUBAF is a cosmopolitan place where international exchange and diversity of opinions are always in the first place, both in research and teaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Press Release&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interview as reported on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=564533849012423&amp;amp;set=pb.100063674375356.-2207520000.&amp;amp;type=3&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Facebook page of TU Bergakademie Freiberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interview as reported on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/Cli0hDkqBqW/?utm_source=ig_web_button_share_sheet&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Instagram page of TU Bergakademie Freiberg &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
